<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Adnane&#39;s Boring World</title>
    <link>https://ghostsdontsleep.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Adnane&#39;s Boring World</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 14:15:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ghostsdontsleep.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Kid And The Owl - Part II</title>
      <link>https://ghostsdontsleep.github.io/posts/post4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 14:15:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ghostsdontsleep.github.io/posts/post4/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Can you stop looking at me with that weird face of yours?&amp;rdquo; asked the owl. Shocking Hades with its ability to speak human language. He dropped his head in disappointment, unable to comprehend what he had just witnessed.
&amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m sorry,&amp;rdquo; the owl continued. &amp;ldquo;I get anxious when someone stares at me.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;So you&amp;rsquo;re not a ghost&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; said Hades in a sad tone.
&amp;ldquo;What? What do you mean I&amp;rsquo;m not a ghost?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Kid And The Owl - Part I</title>
      <link>https://ghostsdontsleep.github.io/posts/post3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2023 11:49:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ghostsdontsleep.github.io/posts/post3/</guid>
      <description>In a late chill night, Hades decided to go out for a walk in the neighborhood, a middle-class type of neighborhood where most neighbors work normal 9 to 5 jobs and seemed to possess little empathy or compassion.
Hades is 10 years old. He has medium-sized black hair and big hazel eyes. He wears a long-sleeved white shirt with blue stripes, a long red scarf around his neck, a pair of black summer shorts reaching slightly above his knees, a pair of brown slippers with some white socks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why are some people good ?</title>
      <link>https://ghostsdontsleep.github.io/posts/post2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 18:59:29 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ghostsdontsleep.github.io/posts/post2/</guid>
      <description>I guess you would much prefer if the title was &amp;ldquo;Why are some people bad ?&amp;rdquo;, this is because we often see questions such as &amp;ldquo;Why are some people evil ?&amp;rdquo;.
We are far more likely to question ourselves &amp;ldquo;Am i a bad person ?&amp;rdquo; rather than &amp;ldquo;Am i a good person ?&amp;rdquo;. Humans give more attention to bad things, and this might be a natural defense mechanism, it&amp;rsquo;s like the brain tries to anticipate bad scenarios to keep you alerted n&#39; help you survive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whoami</title>
      <link>https://ghostsdontsleep.github.io/posts/whoami/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 11:55:40 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ghostsdontsleep.github.io/posts/whoami/</guid>
      <description>Hi, my name&amp;rsquo;s Adnane, I&amp;rsquo;m 22 years old and i work as a Data Engineer. I&amp;rsquo;m passionate about Music, Learning new languages, and Computers (those are the ones I can think of&amp;hellip;). Favorite food ? Noodles. Favorite show ? Mindhunter. Favorite website ? Reddit.
I know this is the internet, and one should be cautious about what information he provides about himself, right? Well, no actually, the internet has already enough information about you (besides your darkest deepest secrets).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
